lodgix.com 2019-05-02

# Vacation Rental Software | Complete Guest Management & Online Bookings for Vacation Rentals, Inns, B&Bs and Hotels

Our formal privacy policy is listed below. In a nutshell, we don't allow third parties access to any of your data contained within the application. Your listing data will be made available to third party vacation rental marketing sites at your discretion. Third party access to this data can be revoked or paused at anytime wthin the Marketing Partners section of the application. 

Thank you for visiting Lodgix.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web [site](https://www.lodgix.com/) only. Links to other web sites, require that you please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

### 1\. Collection of Information

We may collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number;
  * Demographic information, such as age, street address, city, country and zip code
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address; 
  * Unique Identifiers, such as username, account number or password; 
  * Geo location based on IP address;
  * Information about your business, such as company name.

We may also collect, from you, personal information about your contacts such as Name and email address where we can send receipts of your purchases. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site. 

Lodgix.com and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. 

### 2\. Cookie/Tracking Technology

Lodgix may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

### 3\. Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

### 4\. Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

### 5\. Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

By e-mail: support@lodgix.com   
By Phone: 877-593-2083 

By Postal Service:

VRM Solutions, Inc.   
d/b/a Lodgix.com   
116 E. Market St, #202   
Elkin, NC 28621 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

Last modified: May 18, 2018
